这是我们之前见过很多次的图像。我们希望这个机器人做点什么
Here's an image that we've seen many times before. We want this robot to do something
有用，所以我们对末端执行器在三维空间中的位置感兴趣。
useful, so we're interested in where the end effector is positioned in 3 dimensional space.
我们要求机器人工具移动到特定的姿势。
We require the robot tool moves to a particular pose.
我们已经讨论过如何使用逆运动学来计算出什么是关节
We've talked about how we can use inverse kinematics to work out what are the joint
为了使机器人末端执行器处于我们需要做的姿势所需的角度
angles required in order for the robots end effector to be at the pose we require to do
有用的任务。到目前为止我们还没有讨论的是我们如何控制机器人
the useful task. What we haven't discussed so far is how we control the robot so that
关节移动到所需的关节角度。控制机器人手臂的任何一个关节，
the joints move to the desired joint angles. The control of any one joint of a robot arm,
通常有一个看起来像这样的结构。在此图中我们可以看到
typically has a structure that looks something like this. In this diagram we can see that
这是一个循环，这是架构中非常重要的一部分。我们要走了
there's a loop and that's a very important part of the architecture. We're going to walk
通过这个系统，我们将从执行器开始。
through this system and we're going to start with the actuator.
执行器是实际使机器人关节移动的装置，它是电机。该
The actuator is the device that actually makes the robot joint move, it's the motor. The
电机的输出是某个位置，我们有一个连接的机械传动装置
output of the motor is some position and we have a mechanical transmission which connects
电机输出到机器人关节本身。机械传动本身
the output of the motor to the robot joint itself. The mechanical transmission itself
通常是变速箱，在某些类型的机器人中，它可能是电缆驱动器。
is commonly a gearbox and in some types of robot it might be a cable drive.
电机的位置由位置传感器监控，并给出信号
The position of the motor is monitored by a position senor and that gives a signal that
说什么是机器人关节电机的实际位置。系统的输入是
says what is the actual position of the robot joint motor. An input to the system is the
期望的位置和我们想要做的是将电机移动到实际位置
desired position and what we want to do is to move the motor until the actual position
等于所需的位置，这通常是联合控制器的工作
is equal to the desired position and that's the job of the joint controller and typically
这是一个嵌入式微控制器。它是在微处理器上运行的一段代码
that's an embedded micro controller. It's a piece of code running on a micro processor
它为电机提供适当的命令，使实际位置匹配
that provides the appropriate commands to the motor so that the actual position matches
理想的位置。通常是联合控制器的输出
the desired position. The output of the joint controller is typically
一些电子信号。它可能是电压，也可能是脉冲宽度调制波形。
some electronic signal. It might be a voltage or it might be a pulse-width-modulated waveform.
这是电机驱动器的输入，电机驱动器是许多控制的电力电子设备
This is input to the motor drive which is a lot of power electronics which controls
施加在执行器上的电流或电压。
the current or the voltage that's applied to the actuator.
该机器人关节控制系统最重要的部分是这个反馈回路。它的
The most important part of this robot joint control system is this feedback loop. It's
我们将电机的实际位置与所需位置进行比较并计算
where we compare the actual position of the motor with the desired position and compute
一个控制信号到执行器，使这两件事情相等。
a control signal to the actuator to make those two things equal.
在本讲座的其余部分，我们将查看每个元素
In the rest of this lecture, we're going to look at each of the individual elements in
这个图一个接一个。如果你想从这个讲座中获得最大的收益，那就是了
this diagram one by one. If you're going to get the most out of this lecture, then it's
重要的是你有一些必要的先决条件。如果你完成了它将是最有用的
important that you've got some necessary pre-requisites. It will be most useful if you've completed
第一个控制理论本科课程。如果你已经这样做了，那么你会熟悉的
a first undergraduate course on control theory. If you've done that, then you'll be familiar
使用拉普拉斯变换等概念，您就会熟悉诸如此类的概念
with concepts such as the Laplace transform and you'd be familiar with concepts such as
动态系统的两极。如果你是的话，它也会非常有用
the poles of a dynamic system. It would also be really useful if you are
熟悉机电系统的一些基础知识，你知道什么是电机，
familiar with some fundamentals of mechatronic systems that is you know what is a motor,
你知道变速箱是什么，你知道编码器是什么，并且熟悉它
you know what a gearbox is, you know what an encoder is and some familiarity with the
嵌入式控制器的想法。
idea of embedded controllers.